subway.co.in 2019-04-18

# Cookie Policy | SUBWAY.com - United States (English)

LAST REVISED: February 04, 2019

Milford, Connecticut   
USA

At Subway, we want to provide you with information about how we collect and use your personal information. This privacy notice gives a high level overview of our privacy practices, along with how you can contact us if you have any questions.

It’s important that you read our full statement or notice to understand what information we hold, how we may use it, and what your rights are, but if you don’t have time to read it all now, here is a quick summary:

  * We collect information about our customers and users of our services along with our employees, franchisees, development agents and other third parties. The information collected is either personal information (such as your contact information) or non-personal (such as webpages accessed).
  * We only collect the information we need or that would be useful to us to provide you with the best possible service and experience.
  * We do our very best to keep personal information secure.
  * We never sell your personal information.
  * Our websites use cookies to help them work well and to track information about how people use them

To learn more about how we collect, protect, use and share your personal information gathered about you when you interact with the Subway brand online and offline, please select the Privacy Statement(s) relevant to you from those listed above.

Please note: some Subway branded websites and applications may be operated by third parties and do not fall within the scope of this privacy statement, such as franchisee operated websites. For more information, visit the relevant privacy statement(s) at the above link(s).

We use cookies and similar technologies for a wide range of purposes in our websites, applications and email communications to deliver our services and improve your experience. To learn more about the categories of cookies we use (and used by our service providers), what they are used for, and how you can change your preferences, please click the Cookie Policy above.

If you have questions about our privacy practices, you can contact us by emailing [ privacy@subway.com ](mailto:privacy@subway.com) , or by contacting us at:

The Subway® Group’s Privacy Team   
C/o Franchise World Headquarters, LLC   
325 Sub Way   
Milford, CT 06461   
USA   
Telephone Number: [ (203) 877-4281 ](tel:2038774281) or Toll Free: [ 1-800-888-4848 ](tel:18008884848)   
Facsimile: [ (203) 783-7479 ](tel:2037837479)
